jobfox.com 2012-09-25

# The Jobfox.com Privacy Policy

At Jobfox, Inc. ( **“Jobfox”** or **“us”** ), we know you are concerned about your privacy, so we developed this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information. As a guiding principal, our mission at Jobfox is to make a better job marketplace. That means we take the information you provide us and make it publicly available to a lot of people - all in order to help you find the right job. You control what information is made publicly available, so if you do not want us to make certain information publicly available, we give you that option. If you want to protect your identity, we give you tools to help you do that, like the ability to block certain domains from accessing your information. Read on and we will tell you how this all works. 

By registering with Jobfox and/or using this site (the **“Site”** ) or any other site that is operated by Jobfox, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information you agree that you are consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Jobfox Terms of Service. If a term is capitalized and not defined in this Privacy Policy, it is defined in the Terms of Service.

So we are clear about the terminology we are using, when we use the phrase **“Personal Information”** in this Privacy Policy, we mean information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. When we use the phrase **“Non-Personal Information”** in this Privacy Policy, we mean information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. Non-Personal Information does not enable identification of or contact with, individual persons.

##  How We Collect Information

We receive and store information you give us (either through the Site or in some other way). You may choose, as part of the services available on the Site (the **“Services”** ) Service, to enter Personal Information, including your name, street address, email address, credit card number and phone number. When you create your match profile on the Site, we collect categories of information relevant to your profile, including your contact information, information about your experience, education, desired salary, and travel limitations. When you submit a resume to us, we collect whatever information you include in your resume. We do all of this to help us in our effort to help you, find the right job.

As you use our Service, we may also passively collect certain information, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, domain names, access times, and operating system. We also use Cookies, clear GIFs, and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URLs) to gather information regarding the date and time of your use of the Service. This type of information is collected to make our Services more useful to you and to help us improve the Site.

If you feel that the services of Jobfox.com could be useful for a third party you know (e.g. your friends or family members etc), you may use our referral service. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend”s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Jobfox stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

We currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company We currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising on other web sites and how visitors use our Site. To do this, we use web beacons, clear GIFs and cookies provided by our marketing company on this Site. The information we collect helps us learn things like what kinds of customers our Site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our Site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. 

An **“Internet protocol address”** or **“IP address”** is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet access provider when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP address probably varies from session to session. We track IP addresses solely in conjunction with session cookies to analyze our web page flow.

**“Cookies”** are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer”s hard drive while you are viewing a web site. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information.

##  How We Use Information

In general, we use your Personal Information to help you find job opportunities. We also use your Personal Information to contact you and provide you with information that may be useful or interesting to you, including newsletters regarding changes and upgrades to the Services as well as promotional e-mails. By using the Site, you agree to receive this information from us. If you do not want us to send you emails or otherwise contact you, you can always opt out of communications by clicking on the unsubscribe links provided when we contact you. 

From time-to-time, we may create Non-Personal Information from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name and other contact information) that would personally identify you. Generally, we use this Non-Personal Information in statistical analysis to help us analyze patterns in the use of our Services. We reserve the right to use and disclose Non-Personal Information in our discretion.

##  Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites. Jobfox is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

##  Disclosure of Information

We will disclose your Personal Information to employers who may have postings for job openings ( **“employers”** ). We do not control how employers use or disclose information they obtain from us, including Personal Information, and those employers may also share your Personal Information with other employers that may have job openings. Also, if you have come to our Site by following a link from one of our affiliates or business partners or by following a link in an online job posting from a potential employer, they may use the information consistent with their privacy policy instead of this Privacy Policy. Since we do not control how they may use your information, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. In addition, we may disclose your Personal Information to third parties with whom we have a co-branding or promotional relationship, including other job sites and our third party support provider. If you would like to know the third party marketing partners to whom we have disclosed your Personal Information, just let us know and we will tell you. If you would like to opt-out from having your information shared with third party marketing partners, either click on the unsubscribe link provided when we contact you or send an e-mail to privacy@jobfox.com asking to be removed from future third party marketing communications. Jobfox does not own the data collected on our third party support pages. 

##  Disclosure of Information

In addition, we may disclose your Personal Information:

  (a) if such disclosure is made to comply with the law or an order issued by a court or an authorized administrative agency, respond to a subpoena, legal process, warrant, court order or to protect the rights or property of Jobfox or its affiliated companies, prevent a crime, or protect the personal safety or rights of others;

  (b) to our service providers for the purpose of providing services on our behalf, such as customer service (help), credit card processing, information technology services, and hosting services;

  (c) as part of a merger or consolidation, or part of the sale of all or substantially all the stock or assets of the business to which the information pertains; and

  (d) as part of a disposition in a bankruptcy proceeding in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court.

Please be aware that when you voluntarily display or distribute Personal Information on the Site or in other ways, that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. We cannot be responsible for Personal Information you voluntarily display, disclose or distribute on the Site or in any other way.

Although we currently do not have any corporate affiliates, such as a parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “ **Affiliates** ”), we may in the future. We will share some or all of your Personal Information with these Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

##  How to Limit the Ability of Others to See Your Information

Giving you tools to help you protect your contact information is a vital part of our mission. The Services provide you the option to the option to block people accessing the Site from certain domains from viewing your information.

You need to be careful, because your resume or other information you provide to us may reveal your identity. It is up to you to make sure you are comfortable with the information you provide. Jobfox does not have any obligation to modify: (1) potentially identifying information in your Disclosed Profile, or (2) your resume to remove or mask information that may identify you. Your **“Disclosed Profile”** means your Personal Information that Jobfox may disclose to an employer (including your resume) according to the settings you choose in your profile.

##  Employers Use of Your Disclosed Profile

**Note that Jobfox does not have any control over how an employer uses and discloses your Personal Information, including information you provide directly to that employer. You acknowledge and agree that (1) Jobfox does not evaluate any employer’s privacy practices, and (2) Jobfox will not have any liability for any actions of any employer.** You should know that employers to whom we may disclose your Disclosed Profile may share your Disclosed Profile with others.

##  Accessing and Controlling Your Information

We are committed to giving you control over your Personal Information. You may access the Personal Information you provide to us, and may modify or delete that information, by logging into to your account and editing it. If you request that we delete your Personal Information we will, but we may retain Non-Personal Information that was derived from your Personal Information, and we may also retain your Personal Information in our backup files for a period of time. Please remember, however, that if we have already disclosed some of your Personal Information, we can not access that Personal Information any longer and can not force the deletion or modification of that Personal Information by the parties to whom we have made those disclosures.

##  Security

Jobfox is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. In particular, all credit card transactions on our site are conducted using SSL encryption. Even though we have taken steps to ensure that your Personal Information is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorized persons, you should know that we cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information. You assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site and the information you post or access through the Site.

##  User Feedback

If you provide feedback, any such comments and any email we receive becomes the property of Jobfox. We may use feedback for marketing purposes or to add to or modify our Services without paying any royalties or other compensation to you.

##  Changes

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes to it, we will either alert you via e-mail or post an alert on our home page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Service and request that we delete your profile. Continued use of our Service following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. All such changes will apply to previously collected information.

##  Contact

If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [privacy@jobfox.com](mailto:privacy@jobfox.com). 

##  Additional TRUSTe Protection

Jobfox is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.jobfox.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [privacy@jobfox.com](mailto:privacy@jobfox.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

Thank you for using our Site

Jobfox  
7926 Jones Branch Drive, Suite 1100, McLean, VA 22102 

Last Updated: January 22, 2009
